# Antonio J. Franceschi

## **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer with over 2 years of experience coding websites using modern technologies and over 15 years of experience troubleshooting and solving problems in the IT Operations field. In the past year I have also mentored and tutored Web Development Bootcamp students.

Bilingual: English - Spanish

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

#### **Address**

1825 SW 67th CT Miami, FL 33155

## CONTACT

ajfranceschi@icloud.com



305.804.4248



ajfranceschi.com



github.com/ajfranceschi

linkedin.com/in/ajfranceschi

# **EDUCATION**

# **Udemv**

The Complete React Developer in 2020 The Complete Web Developer in 2019 The Complete Web Developer Course 2.0

# edX PennX

SD4x: Programming for the Web with JS

# **Devslopes**

Beginner Full Stack Web Development

# **University of Puerto Rico**

BBA: Business Administration, MIS

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- jQuery
- React Router
- MongoDB
- Sass

- CSS
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- PostgreSQL
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React Redux
- **ExpressJS**
- MySQL
- RESTful API

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
- Responsive Web Design
- Complete React Developer in 2020
- The Complete Web Developer in 2019: Zero to Mastery
- SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript
- Microsoft Certified Systems Administrator
- Apple Certified Macintosh Technician
- CompTIA Network+
- CompTIA A+

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Associate L2, Team Lead, Field Ops

# Lion Re:Sources, Publicis Groupe

2017 - 2020

- Increase productivity of a team of 8 technicians by providing continuous feedback and support.
- Coordinate with vendors the procurement, installation and repair of company owned equipment.
- Increase end user satisfaction and team members productivity by creating and facilitating trainings.
- Lead infrastructure equipment refresh projects.
- Create and maintain Active Directory objects when warranted.

# **Operations Analyst, Field Ops**

# Lion Re:Sources, Publicis Groupe

2011-2017

- Support more than 400 on-site and remote users, including Executives, on Macintosh, Windows and mobile devices.
- Minimized downtime by monitoring servers and networking gear.
- Install and fix server and networking equipment.
- Test new technologies and ensure compatibility with existing environment before placing into production.
- Minimize A/V downtime by troubleshooting and repairing issues.

# **Desktop Support Technician**

## Our Kids of Miami Dade & Monroe

2009-2011

- Provide end user support to over 400 end users.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot Mac and PC equipment, DSL connectivity issues.
- Decrease equipment deployment time to completion by creating and maintaining Operating System images for all our devices.
- Create and maintain Active Directory objects.
- Train newly hired technicians.
- Communicate daily with other IT departments for escalation and coordinate end user support.